bellsouth.net 2006-12-06

# BellSouth Help Center Online - My Help Home

**Online Privacy Policy**

At BellSouth we are committed to honoring the privacy of our on-line customers and visitors to our Web sites. We recognize the importance to you of maintaining an appropriate level of privacy and security for the personal information we collect from you over the Internet. The following discloses our Web site information gathering and use practices and is limited to the protection and use of personal information collected by us in the online environment. Your access to and use of our site are subject to this policy and any other terms of use or policies posted by us. Please note that this privacy statement applies only to this site and not to the web sites of our advertisers or of other companies or organizations to which we link. All references to "BellSouth" throughout this policy statement include, unless otherwise stated, all BellSouth affiliate companies, successors and assigns. 

**What Kinds of Information Does BellSouth Collect and Use?**

The only personally identifiable information we collect about visitors is provided voluntarily. In general, you can visit our Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, some portions of our Web site may be accessible only to users who have registered with us (and who may be asked to provide certain information as part of the registration or login process). In addition, our Web servers may use "cookies" (described below) to collect information about visitors such as domain names, but not your e-mail addresses. This information may be aggregated to measure such things as the number of visits, average time spent on the site, number of pages viewed, and methods by which our site was found. BellSouth uses such information to evaluate the use of our site and to continuously improve the content and services being provided.At times we may ask you for contact information or conduct on-line surveys in order to better understand your needs so that we can provide you with a customized experience. If we wish to use this information other than as set forth in this statement, we will let you know at the time of collection. We will take commercially reasonable steps to safeguard this information from unauthorized access.

At times we may ask you for contact information or conduct on-line surveys in order to better understand your needs so that we can provide you with a customized experience. If we wish to use this information other than as set forth in this statement, we will let you know at the time of collection. We will take commercially reasonable steps to safeguard this information from unauthorized access.

When you access your account information, order a service or make a payment on-line, request product or service information, send us e-mail, register to receive news or information alerts, establish a “My Yellow Pages,” submit a click wrap agreement or enter a contest that we are sponsoring, we will ask you to provide individually-identifiable information to us. Except as otherwise provided below under the heading “Who Has Access to This Information?”, when you supply information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for that purpose and to manage the internal operations and security of our Web site consistent with the terms of use and policies established from time to time governing this site. Such purpose may involve the disclosure of such information to unaffiliated companies/vendors where necessary to and for the limited purpose of processing your request, processing a transaction authorized by you or providing you with products or services.

We also want you to be aware that certain information related to telecommunications services provided to you by BellSouth, commonly referred to as "Customer Proprietary Network Information" or "CPNI," is subject to special Federal laws and regulations, with which we are fully committed to comply, both in the on-line environment and in all other respects. For more information about these special rules and our related policies regarding the use of CPNI, please visit - BellSouth's Public Policy website at <http://bellsouthcorp.com/policy/>.

**Who Has Access to This Information?**

Unless we specifically disclose it to you at the time of collection or subsequently obtain your approval, we will not make visitor or customer-specific information that is gathered on our site available to unaffiliated organizations for commercial purposes unrelated to the business of BellSouth. BellSouth and its affiliated companies use this information to help us deliver the services you have requested, or to design or offer specific products or services that we believe will be useful to you. While we may use this information to contact you or to send materials to you for marketing purposes, we will take commercially reasonable steps to safeguard such information from unauthorized access by any other parties. As we strive to meet the needs or our customers, we may disclose personally identifiable information we collect, as described above, to companies and vendors that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or with whom we have joint marketing agreements so that we may provide a full range of products and services to you. Our policy is to prohibit these companies from otherwise selling or disclosing the personal information we provide.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BellSouth’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

Certain federal, state and local laws or government regulations may require us to disclose non-public personal information about you. In these circumstances, we will use reasonable efforts to disclose only the information required by law, subpoena or court order to be disclosed.

**Cookies**

Our site may make use of cookies (or a similar technology) to better manage our sites and to assist us in providing you with tailored information and services. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which is stored on your hard drive so that we can do things such as better serve you as you navigate through our site or when you return. You may set your browser to notify you or decline the receipt of a cookie; however, certain features of our sites may not function properly or be available if your browser is configured to disable cookies.

**E-Mail**

BellSouth's policy is not to read or disclose private e-mail communications that are transmitted using BellSouth services except to respond, if directed to us, or as required to operate the service, as set forth in the terms of use and policies established from time to time governing the service, or as otherwise required by law.

**Children**

BellSouth recognizes the importance of children's safety and privacy on the Internet. For this reason and to comply with certain laws, we do not intentionally collect personal, individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we offer content targeted to children under 13.Children should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before disclosing any information online. Several software companies can provide children's safety software, including some that may have reduced prices or other special offers for certain BellSouth customers.

**Security**

BellSouth maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect the confidentiality of personal information provided by you at our Web site. For example, unique passcodes or passwords are required to access a number of our Web site services. In addition to requiring the use of a unique passcode or password, all payments processed through our Web site require personal transactional information provided by you to be sent in a "Secure Session" using Secure Socket Layer encryption technology. This technology encrypts - or scrambles - your financial or credit card account information to help prevent unauthorized parties from reading it. We regularly test and update our technology to help protect your personal information. However, such precautions do not guarantee that our Web site is invulnerable to all security breaches. BellSouth makes no warranty, guarantee, or representation that use of our Web site is protected from all viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities and that your information will always be secure. When doing business with others, such as advertisers to whom you can link from our site, you should consider the separate security and privacy policies of those other sites.

**Discussion Areas**

This site may provide discussion areas so that customers and visitors can communicate freely and share ideas. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when disclosing such information. These discussion areas may be monitored occasionally in order to enhance the safety and respect for all of our customers and visitors, and off-topic, unlawful or otherwise inappropriate content of materials of which we become aware may or may not be removed from the site during the course of such monitoring. However, BellSouth is not responsible for any information posted or remaining on these discussion areas. 

**Links to Other Sites**

For the convenience of our visitors and customers, this Web site may contain links to other sites. While we generally try to link only to sites that share similar high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, products or services offered or the privacy and security practices employed by these other sites

**Third Party Ad Servers**

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other web sites, in combination non-personally identifiable information about your purchases and interests from other online and offline sources, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share web site usage information about our visitors to our sites with this company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our site and other sites. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising company may note some of the pages you visit on our site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs) or other similar tracking mechanisms. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer. 

**Revisions**

Because of the evolving nature of the technologies that we use and the way that we conduct business, we may amend this policy from time to time. We will post any revisions on this site.

**Feedback**

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, your dealings with this Web site, or if you find that we have any incorrect information concerning you or any of your accounts with us, you may contact us at [webmaster@bellsouth.net](mailto:webmaster@bellsouth.net).

Back to the previous page
